Guide to the R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company Archive 1844-2005
University of Chicago Library
- Series XVII: Personnel
  - Subseries 3: Training
    - "The Business of Being a Supervisor," 1929 (Box 1014, Folder 2)
    - Business Letter Writing, circa 1960s (Box 1014, Folder 3)
    - "Calendars," Training Library samples collection, early 20th century (Box 1014, Folder 4)
    - A Composition Manual, Printing Industry of America, 1953 (Box 1014, Folder 5)
    - A Composition Manual, Printing Industry of America, 1953 (Box 1015, Folder 1)
    - Composition and Plate-Making, circa 1964 (Box 1015, Folder 2)
    - Corporate and Sales Training, 1992 (Box 1015, Folder 3)
    - A Course in Estimating, Printing Industry of America, 1954 (Box 1015, Folder 4)
    - "A Course in Printing Estimating, Part III: Presswork," 1923 (Box 1016, Folder 1)
    - A Course in Printing Practice I, 1934 (Box 1016, Folder 2-4)
    - A Course in Printing Practice II, 1935 (Box 1016, Folder 5-6)
    - A Course in Printing Practice, Part II: Composition, 1927 (Box 1017, Folder 1)
    - A Course in Printing Practice, Part V: Bindery Operations, 1924- 1928 (Box 1017, Folder 2-4)
    - A Course in Printing Practice, Part V: Bindery Operations, 1924- 1928 (Box 1018, Folder 1-2)
    - A Course in Printing Practice, Part V: Bindery Operations, 1925 (Box 1018, Folder 3)
    - A Course in Printing Practice, Part V: Bindery Operations, 1928 (Box 1018, Folder 4)
    - A Course in Printing Practice, Part VIII: The Book, 1927 (Box 1018, Folder 5-7)
    - A Course in Printing Practice, Part VIII: The Book, 1927 (Box 1019, Folder 1-4)
    - A Course in Selling Printing, Printing Industry of America, 1949 (Box 1019, Folder 5-6)
    - Cylinder Pressmanship, Matt M. Kandle, 1917 (Box 1020, Folder 1-3)
    - "Cylinder Pressmanship," circa 1940s (Box 1020, Folder 4-5)
    - Department B, "The Job and Cylinder Pressroom," 1952 (Box 1020, Folder 6)
    - Department C, "Guide for Operators and Trainees," 1951 (Box 1020, Folder 7)
    - Department K, circa 1967 (Box 1021, Folder 1)
    - "Department M Guide," circa 1960s (Box 1021, Folder 2-4)
    - Department M, "A Guide for Operators and Trainees," 1954 (Box 1021, Folder 5)
    - Department R, "Trainees Manual: Preparation of Artwork and Copy," 1951 (Box 1021, Folder 6-7)
    - Donnelley Printing Processes, Course 2: Offset Preliminary, 1968 (Box 1022, Folder 1)
    - Evening Course Program, Course 1: An Introduction to Printing, circa 1960s (Box 1022, Folder 2-4)
    - "Evening Course - Web Press Folders and Process Evaluation," circa 1960 (Box 1022, Folder 5)
    - "Folder Basics," Frank Drazan and Len Miller, circa 1960s (Box 1022, Folder 6)
    - French Literature, Including Manuscripts, Illustrated Books and Armorial Bindings, Maggs Brothers, Apprentice Library Collection, 1922 (Box 1022, Folder 7)
    - Evening course program, 1963-1964 (Box 1022, Folder 8)
    - "A Glossary of Printer's Terms," circa 1950s (Box 1023, Folder 1)
    - "A Glossary of Printer's Terms," 1982 (Box 1023, Folder 2)
    - "Glossary of Rotogravure Terms," circa 1950s (Box 1023, Folder 3)
    - "Graphics," typeface and paper specimens, Training Library collection, undated (Box 1023, Folder 4)
    - "Handbook for Opaquers," 1960 (Box 1023, Folder 5)
    - "Handbook for Rotogravure Inks," 1967 (Box 1023, Folder 6)
    - History of Printing, "I Am the Printing Press," 1972 (Box 1023, Folder 7)
    - "How to Make a Layout: For Students in Printing," 1935 (Box 1023, Folder 8)
    - "Instructor's Manual," circa 1960 (Box 1023, Folder 9)
    - Lakeside Press Manual of Style, 1948 (Box 1023, Folder 10-11)
    - Lakeside Press Manual of Style, 1948 (Box 1024, Folder 1-5)
    - Lakeside Press Manual of Style, 1948 (Box 1025, Folder 1)
    - "Letterpress Rolltender's Manual," circa 1950s (Box 1025, Folder 2)
    - "Linotype Keyboarding: A Practical Approach to Problems of Instruction," circa 1940s (Box 1025, Folder 3)
    - "Linotype Machine Principles: A Course of Related Study," circa 1940s (Box 1025, Folder 4)
    - "Machine Binding," Ted Mayer, 1969 (Box 1025, Folder 5-6)
    - Management Development Guide, 1989 (Box 1025, Folder 7)
    - Manager Information and Techniques II, 1967 (Box 1025, Folder 8)
    - Manager's workshops and seminars, 1950-1967 (Box 1025, Folder 9)
    - "Manual of Basic Mechanics," Edward Thommen, Jr., circa 1950s (Box 1026, Folder 1)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, 1951 (Box 1026, Folder 2)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Chemistry and Physics of Platemaking, circa 1960s (Box 1026, Folder 3)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course 1: Basic Printing, circa 1950s (Box 1026, Folder 4-7)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course 1: Basic Printing, circa 1950s (Box 1027, Folder 1-2)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course I-II, 1956 (Box 1027, Folder 3)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course I-II: Basic Printing Operations, 1952 (Box 1027, Folder 4)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course I-II: General Printing, circa 1960 (Box 1027, Folder 5)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course III: Photo-chemical Surfaces, circa 1960 (Box 1027, Folder 6)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course III: Printing Surfaces, 1964 (Box 1028, Folder 1-2)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course IV-A, 1952 (Box 1028, Folder 3)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course IV-A: Case Binding - Inspecting, 1948 (Box 1028, Folder 4)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course IV-A: Case Binding - Inspecting, 1959 (Box 1028, Folder 5)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course IV-A: Machine Binding, circa 1960s (Box 1028, Folder 6)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course IV-A: Machine Binding, circa 1960s (Box 1029, Folder 1-2)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course IV-B: Case Binding, 1955-1966 (Box 1029, Folder 3-6)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course IV-B: Tape-Sewn Case Binding, 1951 (Box 1029, Folder 7)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course 5: Composition and Plate- Making, 1964 (Box 1029, Folder 8-9)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course 11: Press Operations, circa 1964 (Box 1029, Folder 10-11)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course 19: Basic Management, circa 1950s (Box 1029, Folder 12-13)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course 24: Industrial Engineering, 1949 (Box 1029, Folder 14)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course 26: Paper and Ink, circa 1960 (Box 1029, Folder 15-18)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course A-2: English for Printers circa 1940s-1950s (Box 1029, Folder 19)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course A-4: Bookwork, circa 1940s- 1960s (Box 1030, Folder 1-2)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course G-1: Basic Mechanics, circa 1929-1950s (Box 1030, Folder 3-4)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Course G-2: Shop Drawing, circa 1950s (Box 1030, Folder 5)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Cylinder Pressmanship, 1946 (Box 1030, Folder 6)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Elementary Photoengraving, circa 1950s (Box 1030, Folder 7)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Practical Composition, 1948-1949 (Box 1030, Folder 8)
    - Manual of Printing Practice, Related Printing, circa 1950s (Box 1030, Folder 9)
    - Manufacturing Improvement Course for Apprentices (Box 1030, Folder 10-11)
    - A Notebook of Printing Practice, 1925-1926 (Box 1030, Folder 12)
    - Offset, Gravure, Letterpress - Printing Manual, circa 1970 (Box 1030, Folder 13-14)
    - Operating Training Program, circa 1970 (Box 1030, Folder 15-16)
    - "Paper Mathematics," Whiting-Plover Paper Company, 1966 (Box 1030, Folder 17)
    - Performance Development Center courses, 1995 (Box 1030, Folder 18)
    - Pocket Pal for Printers, Estimators and Advertising Production Managers, International Paper Company, 1957 (Box 1030, Folder 19)
    - Printing Practice, Course IV-B: Case Binding, 1961 (Box 1030, Folder 20-22)
    - Printing Practice, Course V, Composition and Plate-Making, 1964- 1970 (Box 1030, Folder 23)
    - Printing Practice, Course V, Composition and Plate-Making, 1964- 1970 (Box 1031, Folder 1-2)
    - Printing Practice, Course IX, Tape-Sewn Hand Binding, 1963-1964 (Box 1031, Folder 3)
    - Printing Practice, Course 18A, circa 1950s (Box 1031, Folder 4)
    - Printing Practice, courses, 1954 (Box 1031, Folder 5)
    - Printing Processes: Relief, Planographic, Intaglio, Loren Carter, circa 1950s (Box 1031, Folder 6-8)
    - Proofroom Practice: A Guide to Proofroom Procedure, 1944 (Box 1031, Folder 9)
    - Research and Operations Manual, Printing Industry of America, circa 1950s (Box 1031, Folder 10)
    - "Rotogravure," circa 1950s (Box 1031, Folder 11)
    - Rules for Compositors: Compiled for the Composing-Room and the School for Apprentices of the Lakeside Press, 1915 (Box 1031, Folder 12-13)
    - Sales Group Manual, circa 1970 (Box 1031, Folder 14-17)
    - A Student's Notebook of Printing, circa 1941 (Box 1031, Folder 18-19)
    - The Training Department of the Lakeside Press, circa 1923 (Box 1031, Folder 20)
    - Training and Development Services courses, 1985-1989 (Box 1031, Folder 21-22)
    - Training Handbook, Course D-1: Rotary Rolltenders, 1950 (Box 1032, Folder 1)
    - Training Handbook, Course R-1: Roto Rolltenders, 1949 (Box 1032, Folder 2)
    - Type recognition course, 1954 (Box 1032, Folder 3)
    - Typographic layout, Albert H. Schlag, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 1032, Folder 4)
    - "What Seven Years Have Done," School for Apprentices, circa 1915 (Box 1032, Folder 5)
    - "Zinc and Halftone Colorwork: An Art and Engraving Travelogue," circa 1921 (Box 1032, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 4: Recruitment
    - "Vocational Opportunities in the Printing Industry in Chicago," circa 1910s (Box 1033, Folder 1)
    - "An Eye to the Future: A Handbook for High School Seniors," 1941 (Box 1033, Folder 2-3)
    - "Good Jobs for Unskilled People Open Now at Donnelley's," 1942 (Box 1033, Folder 4)
    - "Get a Job Now at Donnelley's," 1944 (Box 1033, Folder 5)
    - "Homes of Craftsmen at the Lakeside Press," 1944 (Box 1033, Folder 6)
    - "Your Career at Donnelley's," 1956 (Box 1033, Folder 7)
    - "Printers Serving a World Demanding Knowledge," 1960s (Box 1033, Folder 8)
    - "A Career in Printing," 1960s (Box 1033, Folder 9)
    - High school student recruitment, 1968 (Box 1033, Folder 10)
    - "Is Donnelley a Good Place to Work?" 1969 (Box 1033, Folder 11)
    - "The Donelley Craftsman, A Major Contributor to a World Demanding Knowledge," 1971-1972 (Box 1033, Folder 12)
    - "Donnelley is the Nation's Largest and Most Advanced Printing Corporation," 1978 (Box 1033, Folder 13)
    - University student recruitment, 1978-1979 (Box 1033, Folder 14)
    - "Donnelley, Dynamic Leadership in a Dynamic Industry," circa 1980 (Box 1033, Folder 15)
    - Technical recruiting, 1983-1984 (Box 1033, Folder 16)
    - "Engineering Horizons: A Career Resource Guide for Graduating Engineers," 1984 (Box 1034, Folder 1)
    - "Donnelley," 1985 (Box 1034, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 5: Compensation and Benefits
    - Benefits, 1913-1991 (Box 1035, Folder 1-2)
    - Benefits plans, 1976-1982 (Box 1035, Folder 3-5)
    - Benefits plans, 1985 (Box 1036, Folder 1)
    - Benefits plans, "Choices" flexible plan, 1990-1991 (Box 1036, Folder 2-4)
    - Benefits plans reporting, 1953-1989 (Box 1037, Folder 1)
    - Bonus program, circa 1951 (Box 1037, Folder 2)
    - Child and dependent care, 1989-1990 (Box 1037, Folder 3)
    - Dental care, 1977 (Box 1037, Folder 4)
    - Financial planning workshop, circa 1999 (Box 1037, Folder 5)
    - Financial planning workshop, 401(K) plan, circa 1999 (Box 1037, Folder 6)
    - Flex time, 1991 (Box 1037, Folder 7)
    - Guaranteed minimum work week, 1959-1974 (Box 1037, Folder 8)
    - Health care, 1930-1989 (Box 1037, Folder 9-10)
    - Health fairs, 1982-1989 (Box 1037, Folder 11-14)
    - Lakeside Press Mutual Savings Association, 1908-1924 (Box 1038, Folder 1)
    - Lakeside Press Relief Association, 1909-1920 (Box 1038, Folder 2)
    - Life insurance, 1929-1963 (Box 1038, Folder 3)
    - Military policy, 1958 (Box 1038, Folder 4)
    - Payroll distribution, 1959-1989 (Box 1038, Folder 5)
    - Payroll savings and investment plans, 1968-1990 (Box 1038, Folder 6)
    - Pension Fund Trust, Northern Trust Company, 1938-1944 (Box 1038, Folder 7)
    - Results-sharing plans, circa 1980s (Box 1038, Folder 8)
    - Retirement ages, men and women employees, 1970-1971 (Box 1038, Folder 9)
    - Retirement benefits, 1941-1992 (Box 1039, Folder 1-3)
    - Retirement benefits plans, 1951-1969 (Box 1039, Folder 4-6)
    - Retirement benefits plans, 1962-1986 (Box 1040, Folder 1-10)
    - Retirement benefits plans, 1987-1990 (Box 1041, Folder 1-2)
    - Retirement, early, 1971 (Box 1041, Folder 3)
    - Retirement planning, 1999 (Box 1041, Folder 4)
    - Salary and wages, 1956-1991 (Box 1041, Folder 5)
    - Savings and loan associations, 1940-1987 (Box 1041, Folder 6)
    - Scholarship programs, 1981-1992 (Box 1041, Folder 7-8)
    - Separation and severance pay, 1990 (Box 1041, Folder 9)
    - Sickness benefits, 1958-1973 (Box 1041, Folder 10)
    - Unemployment compensation, 1949-1958 (Box 1041, Folder 11)
    - Uniform rental program, 1966 (Box 1041, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 6: Employee Organizations, Activities and Events
    - Anniversaries, 1975-1988 (Box 1042, Folder 1-2)
    - Anniversaries, 25-Year Club, 1950-1992 (Box 1042, Folder 3)
    - Anniversaries, 50-year, 1959-1987 (Box 1042, Folder 4)
    - Anniversaries, Milestones publication, 1992-1995 (Box 1042, Folder 5-8)
    - Anniversaries, Milestones publication, 1996-1998 (Box 1043, Folder 1-3)
    - Blood drive program, 1975-1982 (Box 1043, Folder 4)
    - Book sale, 1964-1978 (Box 1043, Folder 5)
    - Classical music club, 1947 (Box 1043, Folder 6)
    - Donnelley Club Cookbook, 1989 (Box 1043, Folder 7)
    - Donnelley Polish American Printing Company, 5th anniversary, 1999 (Box 1043, Folder 8)
    - Entertainment arrangements, circa 1950s (Box 1043, Folder 9)
    - Graphic Arts Club, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 1044, Folder 1-2)
    - Lakeside Press Choral Society, 1976-1977 (Box 1044, Folder 3)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, 1915-1970 (Box 1044, Folder 4)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, amateur nights and minstrel shows, 1915-1932 (Box 1044, Folder 5)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, annual dances, 1909-1942 (Box 1044, Folder 6)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, annual golf tournament, 1941 (Box 1044, Folder 7)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, annual picnics, 1910- 1941 (Box 1044, Folder 8-9)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, annual picnics, Department A, 1950 (Box 1045, Folder 1)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, Department M, newsletters, 1951 (Box 1045, Folder 2)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, athletic meet, 1916 (Box 1045, Folder 3)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, baseball scorecards, undated (Box 1045, Folder 4)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, constitution and by-laws, 1922-1950s (Box 1045, Folder 5-6)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, entertainment arrangements, 1924-1926 (Box 1045, Folder 7)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, library, 1986 (Box 1045, Folder 8)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, Midway Gardens rental contract, 1924 (Box 1045, Folder 9)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, “Midnight Marauder” newsletter, 1909 (Box 1045, Folder 10)
    - Lakeside Press Employee Association, procedures for handling business affairs, undated (Box 1045, Folder 11)
    - Printers Hall of Fame, 1963-1965 (Box 1045, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 7: Retirees
    - Directories of retired employees, 1961-1980 (Box 1046, Folder 1-6)
    - Directories of retired employees, 1982-1996 (Box 1047, Folder 1-4)
    - Retired Employees Club, 1969-1986 (Box 1047, Folder 5)
    - Retired Employees Club, 25th Anniversary, 1971-1996 (Box 1047, Folder 6)
    - Retired Employees Club, newsletters, 1994-2000 (Box 1047, Folder 7)
    - Retirement tributes and signature book inserts, 1945-1952 (Box 1047, Folder 8-11)
    - Retirement tributes and signature book inserts, 1953-1969 (Box 1048, Folder 1-11)
    - Retirement tributes and signature book inserts, 1970-1974 (Box 1049, Folder 1-8)
    - Retirement tributes and signature book inserts, 1975-1980 (Box 1050, Folder 1-7)
    - Retirement tributes and signature book inserts, 1980-1983 (Box 1051, Folder 1-3)
    - Retirement tributes and signature book inserts, undated (Box 1051, Folder 4-5)
    - Signature book samples, blank, undated (Box 1051, Folder 6- 8)
    - Signature book samples, blank, undated (Box 1052, Folder 1-4)
    - Signature books, production and ordering, 1959-1979 (Box 1052, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 8: Employee Handbooks
    - Employees' Handbook, 1925 (Box 1053, Folder 1)
    - Employees' Handbook, 1930 (Box 1053, Folder 2)
    - Employees' Handbook, 1938 (Box 1053, Folder 3)
    - Employees' Handbook, artwork, 1938 (Box 1053, Folder 4)
    - Employees' Handbook, blank sample, undated (Box 1053, Folder 5)
    - "For the Guidance of Employees," 1949 (Box 1053, Folder 6)
    - "For the Guidance of Employees," 1954 (Box 1053, Folder 7)
    - "For the Guidance of Employees," 1966 (Box 1053, Folder 8)
    - "Plant Rules You Should Know," 1975 (Box 1053, Folder 9)
    - "You and Your Company," 1942 (Box 1053, Folder 10-12)
    - "You and Your Company," Illinois Tool Works, 1943 (Box 1054, Folder 1)
    - "You and Your Company," 1944 (Box 1054, Folder 2)
    - "You and Your Company," Crawfordsville edition, 1945 (Box 1054, Folder 3)
    - "You and Your Company," 1947 (Box 1054, Folder 4-7)
    - "You and Your Company," Detroit edition, 1947 (Box 1054, Folder 8)
    - "You and Your Company," Crawfordsville edition, 1949 (Box 1055, Folder 1)
    - "You're a Donnelley Printer Now," 1974 (Box 1055, Folder 2)
    - "You're a Donnelley Printer Now," 1980 (Box 1055, Folder 3)
    - "You're a Donnelley Printer Now," 1982 (Box 1055, Folder 4)
    - "You're a Donnelley Printer Now," 1985 (Box 1055, Folder 5)
    - "You're a Donnelley Printer Now," 1989 (Box 1055, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 9: Timesheets and Payroll Ledgers
    - Yearly earnings comparisons, 1946-1950 (Box 1056, Folder 1)
    - Timesheets, 1950-1951 (Box 1056, Folder 2-7)
    - Timesheets, 1961-1959 (Box 1057, Folder 1-5)
    - Payroll ledger, January-December 1936 (Box 1058, Folder 1-5)
    - Payroll ledger, July-December 1936 (Box 1059, Folder 1-4)
    - Payroll ledger, January-October 1937 (Box 1060, Folder 1-6)
    - Payroll ledger, August-December 1937 (Box 1061, Folder 1-5)
    - Payroll ledger, January-November 1938 (Box 1062, Folder 1-6)
    - Payroll ledger, August-December 1938 (Box 1063, Folder 1-5)
    - Payroll ledger, January 1941 (Box 1064, Folder 1-3)
    - Payroll ledger, February 1941 (Box 1064, Folder 4-6)
    - Payroll ledger, February 1941 (Box 1065, Folder 1)
    - Payroll ledger, February-March 1941 (Box 1065, Folder 2)
    - Payroll ledger, March 1941 (Box 1065, Folder 3-6)
    - Payroll ledger, April 1941 (Box 1066, Folder 1-3)
    - Payroll ledger, April-May 1941 (Box 1066, Folder 4)
    - Payroll ledger, May 1941 (Box 1066, Folder 5)
    - Payroll ledger, May-June 1941 (Box 1067, Folder 1-4)
    - Factory payroll ledger, July-August 1946 (Box 1067, Folder 5)
    - Factory payroll ledger, January-June 1954 (Box 1068, Folder 1-5)
    - Office payroll ledger, Crawfordsville, 1955 (Box 1069, Folder 1)
    - Salary payroll ledger, 1956-1958 (Box 1069, Folder 2)
    - Salary payroll ledger, Chicago, 1956-1958 (Box 1070, Folder 1-6)
    - Payroll ledger, 1959 (Box 1071)
    - Salary payroll ledger, Chicago, January-June 1961 (Box 1072, Folder 1-5)
    - Salary payroll ledger, Chicago, July-December 1961 (Box 1073, Folder 1-5)
  - Subseries 10: Oversize
    - Lakeside Press Employees Association, annual picnic broadside, 1926 (Box 1074, Folder 1)
    - "Practice for Hand Binding, Apprentice School," instructional broadside, circa 1930 (Box 1074, Folder 2)
    - Lakeside Press Employees Association, annual picnic broadside, 1941 (Box 1074, Folder 3)
    - Journeyman graduation certificates, blank, undated (Box 1074, Folder 4)
    - Wage and benefit announcements scrapbook, 1944-1952 (Box CABINET 2 DRAWER 1)
    - "Donnelley Savers," energy conservation program, broadsides, circa 1970s-1980s (Box CABINET 2 DRAWER 1, Folder 1)
- Series XVIII: Facilities and Operations
  This series documents RR Donnelley buildings, properties, and facilities, as well as day-to-day printing operations that formed the core of the company's activities. Material in this series spans the years 1872-2000, although material is heavily concentrated in the mid- to late twentieth century.
  This series is divided into eight subseries:
  Subseries 1: Building and Properties, contains drawings, brochures, blueprints, and correspondence. This subseries has been organized by building, with files arranged alphabetically and then chronologically. This subseries includes drawings for building layouts and equipment, informational brochures from contractors for printing and utility equipment, and correspondence with architects and contractors.
  Subseries 2: Facilities Management, includes plant site surveys, equipment reports, construction contracts, deeds, leases, and titles related to RR Donnelley's land purchases and construction. This includes correspondence and reports from contractors, copies of deeds and leases and other government documents, surveys of potential plant sites, and reports on printing equipment for plants. This subseries has been arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  Subseries 3: Industrial Engineering, contains materials related to research and development in printing equipment. The bulk of this material is related to RR Donnelley's development of technology and templates for National Geographic magazines. This subseries also includes patent applications and documentation. This subseries has been arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  Subseries 4: Procedure Manuals, contains instructional books detailing the day-to-day operating procedures of RR Donnelley's company plants. These books document company-wide procedures, as well as those for various printing departments within the company. This subseries is arranged alphanumerically and then chronologically.
  Subseries 5: Equipment Manuals and Specifications, contains books detailing the specifications for operating printing equipment, including presses and mechanical folders. This subseries has been arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  Subseries 6: Typeface Specimens, contains indices and samples of various typefaces. These show examples of different typefaces available at RR Donnelley's printing plants. This subseries has been arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  Subseries 7: Alphabetical Files, contains a selection of correspondence, reports, and memos regarding the history, maintenance, and goals of RR Donnelley's printing facilities. This includes a brief history of some plants, reports on the daily operations of facilities, and correspondence regarding proposals and new land purchases. Thus subseries has been arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  Subseries 8: Oversize, contains large blueprints for buildings, equipment, and utilities for RR Donnelley's printing plants, all transferred from subseries 1. File are organized by size, and then by building name.
  Additional materials related to RR Donnelley's facilities and operations are found in Series II, IX, XI, XII, IXX, and XX.
  - Subseries 1: Buildings and Properties
    - 2223 Martin Luther King Drive, air filters, informational brochures, 1960-1962 (Box 1075, Folder 1)
    - 2223 Martin Luther King Drive, architect, correspondence, sketches, information, 1959-1961 (Box 1075, Folder 2)